





DANIEL UNGUREANU

JUNIOR PYTHON DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present

UNGUREANU WEBTECH SRL

DEVELOPER / ADMINISTRATOR

- Own web development company
- Using Python, Django for backends, JS, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS for frontends, cpanel for hosting, AWS for static files, Linux OS user

OBICEIURI SANATOASE SRL

CO-FOUNDER & ASSOCIATE

· Administrative tasks, managing website, google ads, social media presence, product photography.

FUNDATIA CONSERVATION CARPATHIA

2014 - 2018

2017 - present

ASSISTANT MANAGER

· Coordinated most of the field activities in a 5.9 mil euros LIFE+, using ARCGIS 10.2 all along, managed large databases, worked with TerraSync.

MAIN SKILLS

Python Django MySQL HTML & CSS UNIX / LINUX JavaScript **ARCGIS**

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English German



PROFILE

I'm a python developer, nature lover and problem solver! I have a strong passion for tech, a natural sciences degree, a M.Sc., 5 years working with ARCGIS, QGIS, databases, VBA. In 2017 i decided to start learning Python with a local school (www.scriucod.eu), then learned Django and web development on my own. I initially used the skills for personal projects or friends, but then in 2021, i started my own web development business, obtaining a few good contracts by now. My aim for the future is to go deeper into programming, learn new skills, by getting involved in complex and challenging projects. My github portfolio can be viewed here.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Programming Course

SCRIU COD

2017 - 2018

2012

2010 - 3

2010

- 9007

www.scriucod.eu

• A 6 months, unconventional python programming course, where we would learn from actually working on small personal projects, that each of us was free to choose.

Master in Science

TRANSILVANIA UNIVERSITY

www.unitbv.ro

• Used Microsoft Access to manage databases, R and STATISTICA to compute statistical tests and charts, QuantumGIS to generate GIS maps with a large database.

Bachelor in Science

TRANSILVANIA UNIVERSITY

www unitby ro

• The final thesis included lots of statistical tests on a quite significant amount of sampled data. First but minor contact with ArcGIS.